[{
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct translation of “to eat”?",
        "answer": "먹는다",
        "choices": [
            "읽는다 ",
            "그녀",
            "읽는다",
            "먹는다"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct translation of “to read”?",
        "answer": "읽는다",
        "choices": [
            "읽는다 ",
            "그녀",
            "읽는다",
            "먹는다"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct translation of “ate”?",
        "answer": "먹었다 ",
        "choices": [
            "먹었다 ",
            "간다",
            "공부한다",
            "먹는다"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct translation of “to study”?",
        "answer": "공부한다 ",
        "choices": [
            "읽는다",
            "간다 ",
            "공부한다 ",
            "먹는다 "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct translation of “will eat”?",
        "answer": "먹겠다",
        "choices": [
            "먹었다",
            "먹는다",
            "먹겠다",
            "먹는다 "
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct translation of “will walk”?",
        "answer": "ch",
        "choices": [
            "가겠다",
            "가다 겠",
            "사겠다",
            "먹겠다"
        ]
    },

    {
        "question": "You are telling your friend that you ate kimchi. Fill in the blank with the best word conjugation. 나는 김치를 먹__",
        "answer": "었어",
        "choices": [
            "어습니다",
            "을 거야",
            "었어",
            "어야"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "In the future tense of verbs, what is added to the adjective stem.",
        "answer": "겠",
        "choices": [
            "저",
            "그녀",
            "는다",
            "겠"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is added to address people who need high respect?",
        "answer": "습니다 ",
        "choices": [
            "습니다 ",
            "는다",
            "겠",
            "가겠다"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct translation of “studied”?",
        "answer": "공부했습니다 ",
        "choices": [
            "공부했습니다 ",
            "갔습니다",
            "괴여웠습니다",
            "가겠다"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct translation of “was cute?",
        "answer": "괴여웠습니다 ",
        "choices": [
            "괴여웠습니다",
            "갔습니다",
            "공부했습니다",
            "가겠다"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct translation of “will study”?",
        "answer": "공부하겠습니다",
        "choices": [
            "가겠습니다",
            "갔습니다",
            "공부하겠습니다",
            "먹겠습니다"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are telling your boss that you finished your job. Fill in the blank with the best word conjugation. 부장님, 저는 일을 ___.",
        "answer": "했습니다",
        "choices": [
            "했어",
            "했습니다",
            "구구 가가?",
            "제와이피"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "You are talking to your teacher. Fill in the blank with the best conjugation. 선생님, 저는 어젯빔에 공부____",
        "answer": "했습니다",
        "choices": [
            "했어",
            "하습니다",
            "했습니다",
            "하야"
        ]
    }
]